ball2win.com 2015-03-15

# Ball2Win

This Privacy Policy describes the way in which ball2win (otherwise referred to herein as "we" or "us") deal with the information and data you provide to us to enable us to manage your relationship with ball2win.

We will process any personal information provided to us (whether via the ball2win website (the "Website"), the customer application form or any other means) or otherwise held by us relating to you in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. By submitting your information to us and using the Website you confirm your consent to the use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy please do not use the Website or otherwise provide us with your personal information. 

### Information Collected and How It Is Used 

The information and data about you which we may collect, use and process includes the following: 

  1. information that you provide to us by filling in forms on the Website or any other information you submit to us via the Website or email; 
  2. records of correspondence, whether via the Website, email, telephone or other means; 
  3. your responses to surveys or customer research that we carry out; 
  4. details of the transactions you carry out with us, whether via the Website, telephone or other means; and 
  5. details of your visits to the Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data. 

We may use your personal information and data together with other information for the purposes of: 

  1. processing your bets, including card and on-line payments; 
  2. setting up, operating and managing your account; 
  3. complying with our legal and regulatory duties; 
  4. building up personal profiles; 
  5. carrying out customer research, surveys and analyses; 
  6. providing you with information about promotional offers and our products and services, where you have consented; and 
  7. monitoring transactions for the purposes of preventing fraud, irregular betting, money laundering and cheating. 

### Information Storage 

We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your information is kept secure and protected. We will only disclose personal information to other companies within associated or subsidiary companies and to business partners, successors in title to our business and suppliers that are engaged to process such information on our behalf. If you apply for an account with us then to help us make credit decisions about you, to prevent fraud, to check your age and identity and to prevent money laundering, we may use third parties including credit reference agencies who will record any searches on your file. We may also make enquiries of, and disclose details of how you conduct your account to, such agencies, security organisations and any other relevant third parties for fraud and money laundering prevention. 

### Telephone Calls 

Telephone calls to and from our Customer Contact Centre are recorded for training and security purposes along with the resolution of any queries arising from the service you receive.

### Use Of Cookies 

We may use cookies as a means of collecting information from a web server for the above purposes following a customer's use of the Website. If you register with us or if you continue to use the Website you agree to our use of cookies. 

Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve the Website and to deliver a better and more personalised service. Some of the cookies we use are essential for the Website to operate. 

If you want to delete any cookies already stored on your computer or stop the cookies that keep track of your browsing patterns on the Website you can do so by deleting your existing cookies and/or altering your browser's privacy settings to block cookies (the process you follow will differ from browser to browser). If you would like more information on how to do this please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. Please note that deleting our cookies or disabling our future cookies means that you may not be able to access certain areas or features of the Website. 

### Internet-based transfers 

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Some of the data processors engaged to process personal data may be based outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). Therefore, by browsing the Website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our (or our suppliers or sub-contractors) processing your personal data outside the EEA. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your information and data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Disclosure of Information 

We are entitled to share the information we hold on you which includes personal data and betting history with the regulator, sporting bodies and other bodies, including the police, in order to investigate fraud, money laundering or sports integrity issues and to comply with our regulatory duties to the Curacao eGaming Compliance. 

In order to comply with ball2win's legal and regulatory requirements and ball2win's own internal risk management procedures, we will retain information for a period of time (generally not more than six years) after closure of your account. All such information will be held in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Access to information 

You are entitled to access the information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Any access request may be subject to a fee of €10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

### Changes to our Privacy Statement

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and any such changes will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy. If we make any material or substantial changes to this Privacy Policy we will use reasonable endeavours to inform you by email, notice on the Website or other agreed communications channels. 

15 Agustin 2013

Ball2Win is owned and operated by SOMMERVILLE MANAGEMENT CO. LTD. Licensed in Curacao with License No. 1668/JAZ issued to Curaçao eGaming, Authorized and Regulated by the Government of Curaçao.   
Payments are done through KIYU PTE LTD 2, Ayios Pavlos & Kadmos Street • Wisdom Tower • 3rd Floor • Nicosia 1105 • Cyprus
